fruit.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy for the Fruit of the Loom, Inc. Web Site - Corporate Social Responsibility and Sustainability

Fruit of the Loom, Inc. complies with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) through participation in the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield certifications. If you would like more information about how personal data is processed by our European sites, please [click here.](http://www.fruitoftheloom.eu/privacy)

This Privacy Policy Statement (“Policy”) describes how Fruit of the Loom, Inc. handles and secures information we learn about you through our websites (the “Sites”). Unless otherwise provided herein, “we,” “us” and “our” shall mean and include Fruit of the Loom, Inc., and its direct and indirect subsidiary companies, including, without limitation, Union Underwear Company, Inc. d/b/a Fruit of the Loom, Russell Brands, LLC, and Vanity Fair Brands, LP (collectively, “Affiliates”). This Policy applies only to personal information that we collect on-line. For purposes of this Policy, “personal information” or “personally-identifying information” means any information you provide to us on our Sites which can personally identify you, and may include your first/middle initial or name and last name, street address, town or city, state, zip code, telephone number, instant-messenger nickname, blog or other personal website URL, date of birth, e-mail address, user log-in, credit card or debit card information, and any other information which can personally identify you. Please read this Policy carefully. We take your privacy seriously and want to make sure visitors to our Sites understand our Policy and their rights. If you have questions or wish to contact us about this Policy, please direct inquiries to: 

  * Privacy Office
  * Fruit of the Loom, Inc.
  * One Fruit of the Loom Drive
  * Bowling Green, KY 42102
  * 270.781.6400

### What Information Do We Collect?

The information we collect from you depends on what you do when you visit our Sites. Please note that we do not collect personally-identifying information about you when you visit our Sites, unless you choose to provide such information to us. 

We collect personal information you provide to us in connection with purchases you make on our Sites, product ratings and reviews you post to the Sites, and your participation in surveys on the Sites. From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or in other voluntary activities through the Sites. We may request personally-identifying information from you, along with other information, in order for you to participate. Participation in these activities is completely voluntary; therefore, you can elect not to disclose your personal information by not participating in the activity. 

In addition, for each visitor to our Sites, we automatically gather certain information and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol ("IP") addresses, browser type and version, internet service provider ("ISP"), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We collect and store this information on an individual basis and in aggregate, or combined, form. We also collect both user-specific and aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit. 

We take the privacy of children seriously. Our Sites are not directed at children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If a child under the age of 13 has provided any of our Sites with personal information, we request that that child’s parent or guardian contact us and we will delete such information. 

### Cookies

We use both session cookies and persistent cookies or pixel tags on this Site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We may link the information we store in cookies to your personal information in order to provide a faster and more pleasant online shopping experience. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some areas of our Site will be limited. 

We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Site. We use session cookies to record session information, such as which web pages a user has visited, and to track user activity on the Site. We also use session cookies to store any passwords used on the Site (such as a password associated with a user account), so you don’t have to enter it more than once per session. Session cookies expire when you close your browser. 

We use persistent cookies to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Site. Persistent cookies remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your browser’s “help” file. 

**By using our Sites, you consent to our use of tracking technologies as described above.**

### How We Use The Information

We use the information to analyze trends, to administer the Sites, to track users’ movements around the Sites, to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole, and to provide users with additional information and offers. We also use the information to improve the content of our web pages, and to customize the content and layout of our pages. All of this is done with the intention of making our Sites more useful to visitors. Any information about yourself submitted in a “public” area or feature of our Sites may allow members of the general public to view such submitted information and content on the internet, and may be routed through our servers or the servers of one or more third parties on our behalf, and the internet, **and, by submitting such information, you acknowledge that you have no expectation of, or right to privacy with regard to, any such posting.** The security of any information you disclose in public areas or features of the Sites is not guaranteed; you make such postings and disclosures at your own risk. 

### Third Party Disclosures

We do not rent, share, or sell personally-identifying information to third parties. Notwithstanding the foregoing, our Sites may share personally-identifying information with companies that provide support services to us, including a web host or web fulfillment services provider (“Permissible Third-Party Companies”). Such Permissible Third-Party Companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. We do not authorize these Permissible Third-Party Companies to use the information we share with them for any other purpose. Additionally, we may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law; to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations; or to protect our Sites, our businesses and assets, or other users of our Sites or the public, in general. Also, we do share information with our Affiliates. We may buy or sell the ownership interests or assets of parent, subsidiary, or other affiliated business entities or file for, or be subject to an involuntary, bankruptcy or restructuring. We reserve the right to transfer all personal information in our possession as part of any such transaction. Such transferred personal information shall remain subject to the promises made in this Policy Statement. 

We may track, or we may use one or more third-party tracking services to track non-personally-identifying information ("other information") about visitors to our Sites. This other information may be collected through the use of pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs, or other similar technologies; through aggregation; or through other similar means. We may use and disclose such other information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. Please note we may link such other information to personal information about you that we have previously collected. Such combined information will be treated as personal information hereunder as long as it is so combined. 

### California Privacy Rights and Do Not Track Disclosures

Residents of the State of California have the right to request a list of all third parties to which we have disclosed their personal information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes, pursuant to California Civil Code 1798.83. If you are a California resident and request information about the disclosure of your personal information, please send a request to the following address and indicate a preference as to how our response should be sent (email or postal mail):  

  * Privacy Office
  * Fruit of the Loom, Inc.
  * One Fruit of the Loom Drive
  * Bowling Green, KY 42102
  * 270.781.6400

We do not engage in the collection of personally-identifiable information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services. We do not permit third parties to collect personally-identifiable information about you over time and across third-party websites when you use our Sites. 

We do not honor Do Not Track requests.

### Links to Third Party Sites

This Policy applies only to information collected by our Sites.

From time to time, our Sites may link you to other sites (“Linked Sites”) that are not owned by us. We do not control the collection or use of any information, including personally-identifying information that occurs during your visit to the Linked Sites. Further, we make no representations about the privacy policies or practices of the Linked Sites, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these Linked Sites. For example, if you click on a link to Facebook from our Sites, your activities on the Facebook site are governed by Facebook’s policy, not ours. 

Be careful of disclosing any of your personally-identifying information when leaving our Sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Sites and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally-identifying information. 

### Third Party Advertising-Related Vendors

We work with third party companies to assist us with website analytics, such as evaluating the use and operation of our Sites so that we can continue to enhance the Sites and the information contained within. 

Please note that our online and email advertising-related vendors, including but not limited to, Facebook, Google, and Twitter, may use pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs, or other similar technologies in connection with the Sites to help manage our online and email advertising campaigns and strengthen the effectiveness of such campaigns. For example, if a vendor has placed a unique cookie on your computer, the vendor may use pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs or other similar technologies to recognize the cookie during your visit to the Sites and to learn which of our online advertisements may have brought you to our Sites, and the vendor may provide us with such other information for our use. 

We may use third-party advertising companies to target advertisements to you on our Sites, across the web, on your mobile device and on any of your other devices, based on the personal and other information we have collected from and about you, as well as information relating to your and other users’ visits to this and other websites and online services. To do so, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through the use of pixel tags) or recognize an identifier associated with your mobile device. These companies may also use these technologies, along with personal information and other information they or we collect on the different devices you use, to recognize you across the devices you use, such as a mobile device and a laptop or other computer. If you would like more information about these practices, go to www.aboutads.info. To learn about your choices in connection with these practices on the particular device on which you are accessing this policy, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp and http://www.aboutads.info/ to opt out of tracking and targeted advertising using cookies or similar technology. You may download the AppChoices app at www.aboutads.info/appchoices to opt out in mobile apps. You may also click on the informational icon contained within each interest-based ad. 

### Information Access

Upon request we provide visitors to our Sites with access to their own personally-identifying information (e.g., user name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them. We also offer visitors the opportunity to have inaccuracies corrected in all information we maintain about them. You can access this information by sending your request to: Privacy Office, Fruit of the Loom, Inc., One Fruit of the Loom Drive, Bowling Green, KY 42102, or by email to [USPrivacy@fotlinc.com](mailto:USPrivacy@fotlinc.com).. To help us process your request, please provide sufficient information to allow us to identify you in our records. We reserve the right to ask for information verifying your identity prior to disclosing any information to you. Should we ask for verification, the information you provide to verify your identity will be used only for that purpose, and all copies of this information in our possession will be destroyed when the process is complete. 

### Security

The security of your personally-identifying information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it, and to guard that information against loss, misuse or alteration. When you enter sensitive and/or personally-identifying information on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We do not send e-mails asking you to provide or confirm personal information. If you receive such an e-mail, please forward it to [USPrivacy@fotlinc.com](mailto:USPrivacy@fotlinc.com) immediately and then delete it. 

Please note, however, that no usage or method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, we are mindful of the pervasiveness and dangers of spyware, adware, and other threats, so cannot guarantee the absolute security of personal information. 

### Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion and at any time, to amend this Policy. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our Sites following the posting of changes to this Policy will mean that you accept those changes. Under certain circumstances we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Policy, or to request your consent for such changes, by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Sites to sending you an e-mail. 

### Questions/Concerns

If you have questions about this Policy, or if you believe any of our Sites are not following this Policy, you may contact us at the postal address, email address, or phone number listed below.

  * Privacy Office
  * Fruit of the Loom, Inc.
  * One Fruit of the Loom Drive
  * Bowling Green, KY 42102
  * 270.781.6400
